天啊 真是笑死我了
Oh my God, that's so freaking funny.
那是 我写的嘛
I know, right?
你们在笑啥
What?
老爸又出品经典之作 给她讲讲
Dad just wrote another classic one. Tell her.
"经典"可不敢当 不过笑话是这样的
I don't know about "Classic," but here we go.
"如果您想买一幢双层小楼"
"If you're looking for a two-story house,"
"那可真找对人了"
"I'm your man."
"我会在您付款之前讲第一个故事"
"I'll tell you one story before you buy it"
"付款之后再讲一个"
"and then another story after."
哈哈 太经典了
No, you didn't!
今晚是S.C.A.R.B.之夜
Tonight is the S.C.A.R.B..
南加州房产经纪人年度宴会
The Southern California Annual Realtor's Banquet.
我猜他们应该知道这个吧
I think they know what it is.
这可是其他所有
It's the mother of all
住宅地产类宴会的鼻祖
residential-real-estate banquets.
过去五年来 这宴会都是吉尔·索普在主持
Now, for the last five years, Gil Thorpe has hosted,
但凑巧的是
but as luck would have it,
他最近在做一个很恶心的息肉切除手术
he's having a sketchy-looking polyp remove.
所以他们就来找我说 "菲尔上"
So they've asked me to..."Phil in."
-你听出笑点没 -当然
- See what I did? - Oh, yeah.
"菲尔[同音词Fill]"
"Phil."
我可以用这个作开场白吗
You think I should open with that?
当然了 这还用问吗
You betcha. You should.
菲尔一定会颜面扫地
Phil is gonna bomb.
不是说他不幽默 他很自娱自乐
It's not that he's not fun. He is so fun.
只是他的笑话都太冷了
He's just not funny.
在这一点上我也有责任
It's probably my fault,
因为他开口 我必笑
because I laugh at all of his jokes.
皮笑肉不笑
With my mouth not with my eyes.
"我看到优秀的房产经纪人玛格丽特·威尔逊来了"
"I see the great realtor Margaret Wilson is here,"
"看上去比以往更加丰满迷人"
"looking more curvaceous than ever."
"说你那一屁股的债呢“
"Talk about your balloon payments."
歌洛莉亚 我们一定要留着这盘
Gloria, do we have to keep
哥伦比亚对战巴西的足球赛录像带吗
this Colombia/Brazil soccer game?
是滴 我一直都没看完这场
Yes, I haven't seen it yet.
这录像已经录好五个月了
It's been sitting in there for five months.
我是说 我可以告诉你谁赢了
I mean, I can tell you who wins.
那这盘两个小时的
And what about this two-hour
《古董路演》节目录像带又是怎么回事
"Antiques roadshow"?
我今天想把它看掉
I'll watch it today.
好吧 那我要去打高尔夫了
Fine. I'm gonna play some golf.
不行 你还要参加米拉贝尔的女儿的成年礼呢
No. What about Mirabel's daughter's Quinceanera?
完全不知道你在讲神马
I honestly didn't get any of that.
米拉贝尔是你的员工
Mirabel. She works for you.
好吧 然后呢
Okay.
她女儿罗莎芭 今晚要举行成人礼
Her daughter, Rosalba, is celebrating her Quinceanera,
这是她的十五岁生日
her 15th birthday.
她邀请了咱俩 但你完全无视了
She invited us. You just going to ignore it.
我才没有 我一直都记得这码事
Of course not. I get this all the time.
我把这事丢给我秘书了
I throw it on my secretary's desk,
她给了他们一份奥马哈牛排当礼物
and she sends them an Omaha steak.
-唉 杰 -咋了
- Ay, Jay. - What?!
曼尼说得对
Manny's right.
女孩的成年礼在拉丁文化中是灰常重要滴
The Quinceanera is very important in the Latin Culture.
作父亲的要带着他的小公主翩翩起舞
The moment the father dances with his little princess.
我还记得我爸爸拉着我滴手跳舞的时候
Ay, I remember my own father holding my hand.
在场滴人无不内牛满面
There wasn't a dry eye in the cartel.
但那些人不会欢迎我去参加的
But these people don't want me there.
明白吗 他们只是客气一下
See, they're just being polite.
我是他们的头儿
I'm the boss.
你这是自欺欺人
That's what you tell yourself
你就是骑在人民头上作威作福
so you can stay above them.
你就扔给他们一个什么"奥巴马"牛排
You just throw them an "Obama" Steak
然后就打你的高尔夫去了
and run to the golf course.
我可没有高高在上
I'm not trying to stay above them.
我只是不想
I just don't think
去他们那什么"叽里呱啦"的事儿里凑热闹
I have to go all "arriba, arriba" with them.
-因为你比他们都强 -当然不是
- Because you're better than them? - No, of course not.
我是说 我只比其中一些人强点而已
I mean, I'm better than some of them.
乃根本都不认识这些人 对不对杰
Do you even know these people, Jay, hmm?
还是说他们根本就只是乃的垫脚石
Or they're just the backs you step on?
我知道你不肯承认我是一枚杰出人士
I know you like to make me out as an elitist,
但事实上 我相当亲民
but the truth is, I'm close with these people.
那就去参加成人礼 证明给我看
Then prove it. Just go to the party.
好吧 只去一个小时 你来开车
Fine. One hour. You drive.
因为我怕把泊车卡给错人
'Cause I don't want to give my valet ticket to the wrong guy,
这样你就又能唠叨我了
have you all over me.
唉 杰
Ay, Jay.
你到底都是从哪儿钻出来的
Where do you keep popping out from?!
小卡现在又开始健身了
So, Cam has started working out again,
这是 这真的是件好事
which is -- it's -- it's great.
瘦身可以让他自我感觉更加良好
He's feeling good about himself,
而我只想让他健健康康的
and I want him to be healthy,
所以这本来是天大的好事
So it is all good.
只可惜有一件事
Except for one thing.
当当当
Knock, knock.
看看谁来了
Look who's there.
或许世界上真的有人
Maybe there's a person in this world
能把单车热裤穿得好看
who looks good in bike shorts.
但我男人肯定不是其中之一
But my boyfriend is not that person.
可我不能告诉他 因为但凡影射到他体型
And I-I can't tell him because he gets incredibly sensitive
哪怕最不经意的一句话都能让他飙从中来
about even the tiniest comment concerning his physique.
嘿 我明天早上想去上一节动感单车课
Hey, I think I'm gonna take this spin class tomorrow morning.
哦 去吧
Oh, sure.
哦 好吧 我明白你的意思了
Oh, I get it. Message received.
我啥也没说啊
I didn't say anything!
拜托 你就不能像正常人一样跑跑步吗
Okay, can't you just run like a normal person?
你说啥 我在做跑珈
What? It's troga.
这是啥
It's what?
你连"跑珈"都木有听过
You never heard of troga?
我真的很讨厌你这种口气
I hate it when you do that.
啥口气
What?
"你连跑珈都不知道吗"
"You've never heard of troga?"
"你连章鱼都没尝过吗"
"You never tried octopus?"
"你就连那么有趣的事都不知道吗"
"You never did this amazing thing"
"我也是昨天才知道
"I just discovered yesterday
但非得装成自己像是一出生就知道一样"
but I pretend like I've done my whole life?"
总之 "跑珈"是指在跑步机上做瑜伽
So, troga is treadmill yoga.
这可是社交之中必备的哦
It's de rigueur.
我看是蠢蛋社交必备吧
It's de-dorky.
你今天吃火药了
What is your deal today?
不好意思 菲尔今晚要去主持宴会
I'm sorry. Phil is hosting that thing tonight,
他现在正憋在家里写段子呢
and -- and he's been writing jokes.
哎呀
Ooh, yikes.
我就知道
I know.
我真的很担心
And I'm worried he's gonna humiliateself
他会在那些大人物面前丢脸
in front of all those important people.
可是我又不能跟他直说
I can't say anything because --
不用讲了 我了解了
No, no. I get it. I get it. I get it.
因为你的打击会令他倍感沮丧
Because it would hurt him even more coming from you.
没错
Yeah.
其实 我和小卡现在的处境
You know, I'm kind of going through something similar
跟你俩的有点像
with Cam right now.
-你们咋了 -他又开始健身了
- Why? - He's started exercising again.
这是好事呀
Well, that's good for him.
没错 但他一直穿着单车热裤健身
Yeah. He's wearing bike shorts.
你肯定很郁闷
That's bad for you.
而我又是最不能跟他说实话的那个人
And I'm the last person who can say anything,
-因为他实在 -我懂
- because he's... - Yeah.
诶 等等 不是 我有主意了
Okay, wait. No, no. All right.
你看过电影《火车怪客》吗
You know the movie "Strangers On A Train"?
呃 我没看过
Hm, I never saw it.
你连《火车怪客》都没...
You've never seen "Strangers On A --"
我错了 牛片
I'm sorry. Great film.
片中有两个人
But it's these guys
都想杀死自己身边的某人
who both discover that they want someone out of their lives.
然后呢
Uh-huh.
然后其中一个人想了一个完美的杀人计划
So one of the guys proposes the perfect crime.
他们去替对方杀人
They will do each other's murders.
我们也应该这样做
We should do that.
好吧 你是说
All right,
由我来告诉小卡丢掉那条蠢裤子
so I would tell Cam to lose the bike shorts?
假装跟我无关
Keeping me out of it.
我去弄停菲尔的笑话
And I tell Phil to lose the jokes.
我喜欢这主意 我加入
I like it. I'm in.
-太好了 -我加入
-All right!- I am in!
嘿 麦肯齐 等等 我是艾丽克斯
Hey, Mackenzie. Stop it. It's Alex.
我想我们等会
Hey, so I was thinking later we'd --
不用 你想怎样都行
Oh, no. Whatever you want.
等会儿打给我
Call me later!
或者我等会打给你 或者
Or I'll call you later, or --
麦肯齐是谁
So, who's Mackenzie?
你不认识她
You don't know her.
我当然知道麦肯齐
Oh, I know Mackenzie.
漂亮 受人欢迎
Cute. Popular.
我就是麦肯齐
I am Mackenzie.
我简直就是麦肯齐的鼻祖
I invented Mackenzie.
而她把我妹耍的团团转的样子
And the way she's making my sister run around...
还真蛮好玩的 不过
It's -- it's kind of funny, but...
我受不了 家人为重
I can't have it. It's bad for the family.
你干嘛呢 我正要打电话给
What are you doing? I was about to call --
麦肯齐 我知道
Mackenzie? Yeah, I know.
现在闭上你的嘴 让我来帮你
Now shut up and let me help you.
这个世界有两种人
The world is divided into two groups --
酷女孩儿和像你这样的女孩儿
cool girls and girls like you.
而你正有一个千载难逢的机会
And you have been given a rare opportunity
能够从前者变为后者
to move from the former to the latter.
是从后者变为前者吧
The latter to the former.
管它呢 天啊 你还真够二的
Whatever. Oh, my god. You're such a geek.
你现在是想要聪明还是要受人欢迎
Now, do you want to be smart, or do you want to be popular?
我想要受人欢迎
I think I want to be popular.
你当然想啦
Of course you do.
但你不能表现的太明显
You just can't be so obvious about it.
你给麦肯齐太多主动权了
You've given Mackenzie way too much power,
你自己得拽起来
and you need to take some of that power back.
是她的
It's her.
把电话给我
Give me the phone.
你就这么说
Here's what you're gonna say --
麦肯齐 我很忙 等会儿你再打来
"Hey, Mackenzie. I'm busy. Call me back later."
-然后你就挂断 -绝对不行
- Then you hang up.- No way!
那你就再也拿不回这手机了
Then you're not getting the phone back.
把它给我
Just give it to me.
麦肯齐 我很忙
"Hey, Mackenzie. I'm busy.
等会儿你再打来 然后你就挂断
Call me back later." Then you hang up.
-我做不到 -就这么做
- I can't. - Do it.
-不行 - 就这么做
- No! - Do it!
好吧 去你的
Okay! Damn you.
麦肯齐 我很忙 等会儿你再打来
Hey, Mackenzie. I'm busy. Call me back later.
太难了
That was hard.
要是容易的话 谁都能受人欢迎了
If it was easy, everyone would be popular.
有人敲门啦
Knock knock!
进来吧 门没关
Come on in! It's open!
我带了些旧的童装来给莉莉
I just wanted to drop off these old baby clothes for Lily.
好的 你人太好了
Oh, that's right. You're so sweet.
我希望自己来的别不是时候
I hope I didn't come at a bad time.
一点也不
Not at all.
我正考虑要带莉莉去哪儿骑车呢
I was just deciding where to take Lily for our bike ride --
湖边还是公园
The lake or the park.
我比较倾向于去公园
I'm leaning towards the park.
我看得出来
I can see that.
你太客气了
You didn't have to do that.
你们还真是传统
You guys are a touch old class.
-今晚对你很重要 -法国红酒
- Well, it is a big night for you, so. - French.
这些家伙啊
Those guys.
那你想好要说什么了吗
So, have you given any thought to what you might say?
事实上 我现在正努力不让自己想这事
Oh, actually, I'm trying not to think about my act right now.
说实话 我内心有点挣扎
I'm kind of fighting the old butterflies, to be honest.
很正常
That's normal.
我听说乔纳斯兄弟在每次演出前都会害怕
I hear The Jonas Brothers get scared before every concert.
凯文不会的吧 那家伙可摇滚了
Not Kevin? The guy's a rock.
尤其是凯文
Especially Kevin.
我真不敢相信我居然给艾丽克斯买过这个
I can't believe I ever bought this for Alex.
我真希望当时有人能说点什么
I wish somebody had said something.
别这样啦 这衣服十年前可能很可爱呢
Oh, come on. That was probably cute 10 years ago.
不 不 从来没有
No, no. It never was.
你知道的
And you know --
我的衣服也是这样
I'm the exact same way about my clothes.
大多数时候 很不错
Most of the time, great.
不过时不时的就会有那么一件例外
But every now and again, there's that one outfit.
我真希望当时有人能对我实话实说
I just wish somebody would be honest with me and say,
你的穿着实在是雷人哇
"What you're wearing is inappropriate."
你懂我意思吗
Do you know what I mean?
我懂 克莱尔
I think I do, Claire.
我懂
I think I do.
我的回答是没问题
And my answer is yes.
好的
Okay.
我愿意给你打扮
I would love to dress you.
不 我不想要你来帮我打扮
No, it -- I don't want you to dress me.
不用
No.
我觉得我该对你坦白
And...I owe it to you to be honest,
所以我要说
so I'm just gonna say
你得丢掉这条单车短裤
that you need to lose the bicycle shorts.
你说什么
Excuse me?
小卡 它不适合你
They're not working for you, Cam.
我不是在针对你
Please don't take this personally.
我是说 没人穿单车短裤好看的
I mean, nobody looks good in bike shorts.
我只是 我觉得我应该对你坦白
I just -- I feel that I owe it to you to be honest.
这么说 我们还是好朋友 对吧
So, we're good, right?
-我们非常要好 -我们非常要好
- We're great. - We're great.
-我们非常要好 -太好了
- We're great. - Oh, great.
好吧
Okay.
或许你应该穿自己的衣 让别人去说吧
You should probably just show yourself out.
我听见 我听见走廊上有哭声
I hear -- I hear some crying down the hallway.
瞧 真是个好父亲
Look at that. That's a good dad.
因为有了孩子
Because you've got a baby,
所以一丁点儿小的声音你都能听到
and you hear every little sound.
要是我的话 我根本就不会注意到
I wouldn't have -- I wouldn't have even noticed...
有哭声
crying.
好了
Uh, okay. All right.
你们需要知道的是
All you need to know about this one
斯基普·乌森是个著名的房产经纪人
is that Skip Woosnum is a well-known realtor
而且很老了
and he's old.
收到
Got it.
斯基普·乌森 房产经纪人 老的
Skip Woosnum. Realtor. Old.
开始了
Here we go.
我不是要说斯基普·乌森已经老了
I'm not saying realtor Skip Woosnum is old,
不过他卖出去的第一件物业
but the first property he ever sold...
居然是个洞穴
was a cave.
你没有
You're not, uh...
没有笑
not laughing.
你怎么不笑 米奇尔叔叔
Why aren't you laughing, uncle Mitchell?
因为他觉得不好笑
'cause he doesn't think it's funny,
或者可能你觉得我并不搞笑
or maybe -- maybe you don't think I'm funny.
你是要说这些吗 米奇
Is that what you're saying, Mitch?
不是
No, it's...
我懂了 我懂了
I just got it!
洞穴
Oh. Cave!
-这个是需要点脑力 -没错没错
- That one's kind of a thinker. - Yes!
他也来了
There he is.
好了
All right, now.
少来了 杰
Knock it off, Jay.
这儿你一个人的名字都叫不出来
You don't know anyone's name here.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
卡洛斯
Carlos!
运气不错
Lucky guess.
还好只有一个人回头
I'm lucky only one turned around.
听着 我需要帮助
Listen -- I need a favor.
我高估了这个派对上我认识的人数
I overestimated the number of people I know at this party.
你去到处转转 做做自我介绍
So you go around, introduce yourself,
我就在旁边偷听他们叫什么
and I'll hear the names.
你知道你是在叫我
You realize you're asking me
帮你证明我亲妈是错的
to help prove my own mother wrong.
你每介绍一次 我就给你两美金
I'll pay two bucks per introduction.
好吧 那是拉蒙纳
All right, well, that's Ramona.
她狂爱饮烈酒
She's crazy for bingo.
拉蒙纳
Ramona.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
别那么不合群了
Stop being such a snob.
过来见见我的朋友夏利奥和他的太太
Come over and meet my friend Julio and his wife --
对不起 你说你叫什么
uh, I'm sorry. Your name again?
凯
Kay?
我觉得你跟凯会很合得来的
I think you're really gonna hit it off with Kay!
我是说 她要教我怎么打扮吗
I mean, she's gonna tell me how to dress?!
她应该干点她更擅长的
She ought to stick to things she knows more about,
像是怎么把三文鱼烤焦
like overcooking salmon.
好吧 等等
Okay, wait.
那么 她真的跟你说
So, she actually said
你穿单车裤不好看吗
that you don't look good in bicycle shorts?
是的
Yes.
你穿单车裤不好看
"You don't look good in bicycle shorts".
疯了
Madness.
是她
Oh, and here she is.
好吧 我不能在这待着了
Okay, you know what? I can't be here.
我要 我要出去透透气
I'm -- I'm going out for some air.
好的 去吧 我也许会跟她吵起来
Yes. Yes, go. This -- this could get ugly.
你好 克莱尔
Hello, Claire.
你这个没种的家伙
You are a gutless weasel.
是的 不
Oh, yeah. No.
我知道你跟我男人说了什么
I heard what you said to my boyfriend.
你跟菲尔说他超搞笑的
You told Phil he was hysterical!
你说他是新一代的理查德·普赖尔
You said he was this generation's Richard Pryor!
你该道歉的人不是我
Well, I am not the one that you need to apologize to.
你在胡说什么 你欠我一个谋杀
What are you babbling about? You owe me a murder.
好吧 克莱尔 我做不来
Okay, Claire, I c -- I couldn't do it.
我没办法打破菲尔的美梦
I couldn't crush Phil's dreams.
我们说好了的 我跟小卡说单车裤的事
We had a deal. I told Cam about the bike shorts.
不 不
No! No!
我们说好的是 你让小卡脱掉那条热裤
The deal was to get Cam to take off the bike shorts.
可结果呢 他还穿着那条愚蠢的单车热裤
But guess what -- he is still in the stupid bike shorts.
我待会打回给你好吗
Can I call you back?
小卡原来一直都在
Turns out Cam was here the whole time,
他听到了我说的话
and he just heard everything I said.
他跑到卧室里哭去了吗
Ooh. Did he just run into the bedroom and cry?
是啊 好像所有同性恋男人都这样
Oh, yes, 'cause that's what all gay men do.
我们都如此软弱
We all dissolve into --
好吧 他还真就这么做了
Yes. That is what he did.
每段婚姻都有一些挑战
There are challenging moments in every marriage.
为了你丈夫不在众人面前出丑
Um...having to tell your husband that he's not funny
而必须告诉他 他其实一点也不搞笑
so that he won't humiliate himself
这绝对是最难的挑战之一了
has to be one of the toughest.
于是我就换了种方式
So I went a different way.
别再说了
Stop talking.
我只是需要时间来让这个伤口结疤
I just need some time for this wound to become a scar.
对不起我把克莱尔也扯了进来
I'm sorry I got Claire involved,
但是 我不是想批评你
But -- and this is not a criticism,
但是有时候你对你的外型
but sometimes you can be a little sensitive
太过于敏感了
about your...appearance.
这就是批评
Well, this is a criticism --
有时你对所有事情都太不敏感了
sometimes you can be insensitive about everything.
我只是觉得 我们的感情足够坚固
I just can't -- I just feel like
经得起一点坦诚的考验
our relationship's strong enough to survive a little candor.
如果我有什么让你不满意的
I mean, look, you could tell me
你就可以直说
if there's something about me you'd like to change.
我讨厌你的胡子
I hate your beard.
你还留了这么一手
Well, you had that bullet in the chamber.
我从来没说过 是因为我不想伤害你
I never said anything because I never wanted to hurt you...
但是我一直觉得你的胡子很烦人
but I've always found your beard off-putting.
是吧 小心脏疼死了吧
See? Hurts.
米奇尔
Mitchell?
米奇尔 回来
Mitchell, get back here!
你在干吗
What are you doing?
我要把胡子剃了
I'm shaving off the beard.
你认真的吗
Seriously?
当然 我家男人不喜欢 那就剃掉
Yeah, well, the man I love doesn't like it, so off it goes.
好
Well, good.
-好的 -很好
-Good. - Great.
很好 那好
Great. Okay.
一
One...
二
two...
三
three.
住手
Wait!
对我来说 你肯这么做已经足够了
The fact that you're willing to do it is enough for me.
我爱你的胡子
I love your beard.
我喜欢你喝卡布奇诺时 会沾上奶油
I love that when you drink cappuccino, you get foam in it
还有你紧张的时候
and when you're nervous, your little...
你的小胡子会抖
hairs twitch.
你就不能在我刮掉这块之前说吗
Well, you couldn't have told me before took a notch out?
对不起 听着
I'm sorry. I -- I -- listen.
我知道 我对于这个 有些太敏感
I know... I can be touchy about... this.
但是你是个超级大帅哥
But you're this amazing-looking guy, and --
我不帅
I am not amazing -
是实话吗
Really?
我不想改变你的任何一点
I wouldn't change anything.
你要知道我每天醒来
You should know that every day,
都因为我的生命中有你而心怀感激
I wake up very grateful to have you in my life.
我才是幸运儿 帅哥
I'm the one who got lucky, handsome.
也许是我表达的不够
Maybe I just don't show it enough.
你可以服务一下我的肩膀作为补偿
Well, you can make it up to me by doing my shoulders.
当然
Sure.
我是指按摩 你在想什么
I meant a massage. What are you saying?
米奇尔 米奇尔
Oh, Mitchell. Mitchell.
是麦肯齐
It's Mackenzie.
又是她
Again.
她想让我参加她办的派对
She wants me to come to this party she's throwing.
她之前发过短信给我
She texted me earlier.
你回她短信了 对吧
You texted her back, right?
才没有
No.
我感到
I'm...
孺子可教也
proud?
-跟她说你会尽量抽时间去 -好
- Tell her you'll try and come. - Right.
然后等她说
And then when she says --
海莉
Haley...
我知道怎么做
I got this.
你是哪位
Who's this?
干的漂亮
Brilliant.
不 我没看到 我短信太多了
No, I didn't see it. I get a lot of texts.
果然是姐妹
I have a sister.
派对是什么时候
When's the party?
我会尽量抽空去
I'll try and come.
你知道我很忙的 我有自己的生活
You know, I'm kind of busy. I have a life.
有很多事做
You know, stuff.
还有作业
Homework.
完了
Uh-oh.
我是说 作业算什么
I mean, not homework.
对于爱学习的人来说 算什么呀
It's not work if you love it.
天啊 挂掉 挂掉
Oh, god. Hang up. Hang up.
闭嘴
Shut up!
没说你 麦肯齐
Not you, Mackenzie.
赶紧把电话扔地上踢过来
Drop the phone and kick it over here!
我得挂电话了
Um, I have to go.
晚点我再打给你
I-I'll call you later.
或者你打给人家也行
Or you call me later.
爱你
Love you!
发花痴
Aah! Aah!
跟着发花痴
刚才还在呢
They were right in here!
我知道 我们哪都找遍了
I know, and we looked everywhere, honey,
要淡定
so just calm down.
淡定皆浮云
Are you kidding me? "Calm down"?
一分钟后
In one minute,
我就要上台了 就像一个
I'm gonna be standing up there like...
像个
like a...
天哪 我词穷了
Oh, my God. I have no material at all.
没事 你一定行的 你不需要准备笑话的
Okay. You're gonna be fine. You don't need jokes.
听我说 亲爱的
Listen to me, honey.
走上台去 展现自己迷人的那面
Get up there. Be your charming self.
发自肺腑地来个自我介绍
Make the introductions from your heart, and get out.
你会表现得很犀利的 好吗
You're gonna -- You're gonna be amazing, okay?
菲尔·邓菲
Phil Dunphy.
上吧 上吧
Go. Go.
各位晚上好
Good evening.
我今天之所以
I would not be here tonight
能够站在这里讲话
if not for the hard work
多亏了南加州房产经纪人董事会的大力支持
of the S.C.A.R.B. Board of trustees...
我的笑话没了
I didn't have my jokes.
除了直抒胸意以外还有别的选择吗
What choice does a guy have but to play it straight?
来自家庭的支持
...the support of my family,
以及吉尔·索普的结肠
and Gil Thorpe's colon.
不过菲尔·邓菲可不是那种直抒胸意的人
But Phil Dunphy is no straight guy.
今晚在坐的有这么多地产经纪业的巨匠
So many giants of residential real estate here tonight.
当然 还有小小约翰麦克宾
And, of course, J.J. McCubbin.
我不是说小小麦是个头矮小
I'm not saying J.J. is small,
但在房地产业界 他被描述为犀利哥
but in the realty section, he was described as "Charming."
马克·西蒙 你在吗
Mark Simon, you out there?
马可在那 你好吗 伙计
There's Mark. How are you, buddy?
马可最近住进了一套新的样板房
Mark recently moved into a new model.
过得如何 家庭妇男
How are you, Francine?
我开玩笑的 马克·西蒙
I kid, Mark Simon. I kid, Mark Simon.
你懂的
You know that.
特兰西科 小马努 还有卡洛斯 这是我妻子歌洛莉亚
Trancito, Little Manuel, and Carlos, my wife, Gloria.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
我们得谈谈
We have to talk.
失陪下
Un momento.
好的
Mm.
我知道吗 我
You know, I --
真不敢相信你完全没印象
I can't believe you never met them.
你从没接触过这里的任何人
You've never met any of these people.
这房间所有的人你都不认识
You don't know anyone in this room.
走吧 杰
Vamos, Jay.
要走也要在父女共舞后再走
I'm not leaving before the father/daughter dance.
此外 你所谓的这些人
And "These people," As you call them,
不仅仅是雇员
are not just employees.
是个大家庭 或者称为家人
They're mi familia, or "My family."
我懂我的母语 杰
I know what "Mi familia" is, Jay.
他说的我可听不懂
Oh, I was afraid of this.
别去 杰
No. Jay. No.
谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you.
女士们先生们 非常感谢你们
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. Thank you very much.
我简单说几句
I'm gonna make this brief.
我知道你们中的大部分人甚至不知道我是谁
I know a lot of you out there don't even know who I am.
正如我的爱妻歌洛莉亚所指出的那样
As my lovely wife, Gloria, pointed out,
错不在你们 在我
That's my fault, not yours.
我是杰·普里契特
I'm Jay Pritchett,
你们的老板
El jefe.
听着 在如此欢乐的时刻
Listen -- on this very, very happy occasion,
今天我请客
I'd like to pick up the tab on the bar.
你们知道吗 在我建立公司之初
You know, when I started this company...
我所 的第一件事
...the first thing that I --
怎么
What?
对了 很好 是的 现在
Oh, right. Right, now. Good. Yeah.
今晚我不是主角
This is not about me.
主角是一位非常出众的年轻女士
This is about a very special young lady
以及一位世上最爱她的男人
And the man who loves her more than anyone else on earth.
多温馨啊
Isn't that lovely?
那是件多有爱的事情啊
That's a beautiful, beautiful thing.
你们知道吗 这让我想起了
You know, I'm reminded
当初我和我的小宝贝一起跳舞
of when I used to dance with my little girl.
不过不是像这样
But not like that.
悠着点 男孩
Slow down, there, muchacho.
别别别别别昏昏昏昏昏昏
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
难道你们在为此喝彩吗 你们在为此鼓掌吗
What, are you applauding this? You're applauding this?
我才不管这是哪门子传统
I don't care what kind of tradition this is.
给我停下 听到没 停下
This is gonna stop. Hey, hey, hey, hey. No!
什么 难道只有我目睹这一幕吗
No! What? What? Am I the only one seeing this?!
我们
V-v-vamos!
亲爱的 我很认真的告诉过你
I mean, honey, I am not kidding when I tell you
坐在我旁边的那个女人都笑岔气了
There was a woman next to me gasping for breath.
真的 菲尔 你太搞笑了
Seriously, you were so freaking funny, Phil.
我有看过专业喜剧演员的演出
I have seen professional comedians
也没有如此笑开了锅
Who could never have done that.
你真是一直被模仿 从未被超越啊
You were unbeliev--
我知道是你拿走了我的索引卡片 克莱尔
I know it was you, Claire. You stole my index cards.
对不起 真的对不起
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我以为我是在保护你
I thought I was protecting you.
如果我的计划成功的话
And if my plan had been successful,
那我就夺走了你今夜的辉煌了
I would have robbed you of the greatest night ever.
对不起 我真讨厌
I'm sorry I'm awful.
才没呢
You're not awful.
是吗
Mm...
克莱尔
Claire...
我就爱你处处为我着想这点
I love that you're looking out for me,
也知道你为什么要担心我
and know why you worry about me.
但我对今晚早就胸有成竹了
But I knew I had this tonight.
我知道了
I know.
只是有的时候我觉得
Sometimes I just think my job
我的工作就是防止邓家人栽跟头
Is to make sure you guys don't fall on your faces.
这对邓菲家族的人来说可不是件容易事儿
That's a hard job in the Dunphy house.
我们丢人是常事
We fall a lot.
我知道
I know.
也许你真正的工作是给予安慰 重树我们的信心
Maybe your real job is to be the person who picks us back up.
这方面没人比你更在行了
Nobody does that better than you.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
我没有朋友
I have no friends.
该你出马了
You're on the clock.
好吧
All right.
出什么事情了
What happened?
我的天哪 老妈 笑死我了
Oh, my gosh, mom. You're killing me.
很好笑 对吧
It's pretty good, right?
好笑 你都可以去拉斯维加斯
Pretty good? You could be, like, in Vegas.
好吧
Well...
这神马情况
W-w-what's going on there?
老妈刚给我模仿了下
Mom does the funniest impression
那天在超市碰到的怪阿姨
Of that weird lady at the supermarket.
我认识她 说来听听
Oh, yeah. I know her. Let's hear it.
好的
Okay. Um...
如果你买两罐泡菜的话
"It's cheaper
会更便宜
if you buy two jars of pickles."
简直活灵活现
It's like she's right here!
我懂了
I know! Yeah.
听起来就像原景再现似的
So like she's right here! I know.
其实一点都不像
That's not what she sounds like.